<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>poster on Thomas Sostarics</title>
    <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/categories/poster/</link>
    <description>Recent content in poster on Thomas Sostarics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.tsostarics.com/categories/poster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Adjective use by individuals with agrammatic primary progressive aphasia</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2020_snl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2020_snl/</guid>
      <description>Sostarics, Thomas; Walenski, Matthew; Mesulam, M. Marsel; Thompson, Cynthia K (2020). Adjective use by individuals with agrammatic primary progressive aphasia. Society for the Neurobiology of Language 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Nonetheless&#39; can reverse predictions immediately: evidence from ERPs</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2019_amlap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2019_amlap/</guid>
      <description>Arkhipova, Yana; Sostarics, Thomas; Law, Ryan; Xiang, Ming; and Chow WingYee (2019). &amp;lsquo;Nonetheless&amp;rsquo; can reverse predictions immediately: evidence from ERPs. AMLAP 2019. Moscow, Russia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accommodation of Rising and Falling Intonation in American English</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2023_midphon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2023_midphon/</guid>
      <description>Design inspirations: Bust a Move. Rubiks cubes. iMessage.
Sostarics, Thomas; Cole, Jennifer (2023). Accommodation of Rising and Falling Intonation in American English. 28th Midcontinental Phonetics and Phonology Conference. Purdue University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Epistemic meaning and the LLL tune in American English</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2022_tai/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2022_tai/</guid>
      <description>Design inspirations: Ribbons.
Sostarics, T., Cole, J. (2021) Epistemic Meaning and the LLL Tune in American English. Proc. 1st International Conference on Tone and Intonation (TAI), 11-15, doi: 10.21437/TAI.2021-3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Voice Quality of Nuclear Tunes</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2022_midphon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2022_midphon/</guid>
      <description>Sostarics, Thomas; Cole, Jennifer (2022). Exploring the Voice Quality of Nuclear Tunes. 27th Midcontinental Phonetics and Phonology Conference. Washington University of St. Louis.
Poster available as a high-definition PNG file. The original PDF has a lot of geometry from the faceted graphs, and as a result has a tendency to crash PDF viewers.
On the poster, there are flags with numbers. Flags on the left column of the poster () denote specific goals/questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing the Locus of Speech-Act Meaning in English Intonation</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2023_icphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2023_icphs/</guid>
      <description>Design inspirations: Riemann sums. Halftone patterns. Northwestern purple &amp;amp; ICPhS blue. Whiteboards. Handwriting. Sostarics, T., Cole, J. (2023) Testing the Locus of Speech-Act Meaning in English Intonation. Proc. International Congress of Phonetic Sciences (ICPhS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tonal center of gravity predicts variation in the interpretation of rising and falling intonation in american english</title>
      <link>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2023_asa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.tsostarics.com/research/2023_asa/</guid>
      <description>1st Place Best Paper in Speech Communication Award
Design inspirations: Magenta. Flattening. Kirby. ASA color palette. Name tags.
Sostarics, T., &amp;amp; Cole, J. (2023). Tonal center of gravity predicts variation in the interpretation of rising and falling intonation in American English. The Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 153(3_supplement), A78–A78. https://doi.org/10.1121/10.0018225</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
